So I'm pretty confident that within the next year, the United States and Israel will form
a covenant that exists on a more overt level than the covert one that already is in place
that essentially identifies Israel as the United States. I am also confident that many Black people
here in the United States and in the Caribbean do not see this as an imminent threat that concerns
them for a multitude of reasons, namely because they may consider themselves to be Christian
and somehow think that it's some sort of safety net, but also because they consider themselves
to not be in the eye of Zionist hatred. And what I want to say to that is that the aforementioned
covenant that's being formed is one between white nationalism and Zionism.
And so they will continue to serve each other with the latter eventually taking over in
full power. And I'm not even sure that the former, the white nationalists even see that
coming, but I do. The world war that's going to come is in the fact that the surveillance
that has been practiced and the oppression and repression that's been practiced on Palestinians
for the last 75 years is going to be done on a global scale. The only hope I have in fighting that
is not necessarily in the people, but in the hope that the earth itself
actually defends us. And so we need to start doing better to defend the earth itself.
You didn't know it was going in that direction, did you? Climate.
Come on out, be in community, buy a book and get it signed. RSVP at amandaseals.com.